const STORE = [
{
  question: 'How many episodes were there in the first season?',
  answer1: '13',
  answer2: '19',
  answer3: '29',
  answer4: '35',
  correctAnswer: '29',
},
{
  question: 'Who was the first character to be on the receiving end of the famous Spock nerve pinch?',
  answer1: 'Pavel Chekov',
  answer2: 'James Kirk',
  answer3: 'Leonard McCoy',
  answer4: 'Hikaru Sulu',
  correctAnswer: 'James Kirk',
},
{
  question: 'Which animals kept interrupting the filming of the first pilot?',
  answer1: 'Racoons',
  answer2: 'Seagulls',
  answer3: 'Rats',
  answer4: 'Pigeons',
  correctAnswer: 'Pigeons',
},
{
  question: 'In which century does the show take place?',
  answer1: '25th century',
  answer2: '23rd century',
  answer3: '22nd century',
  answer4: '21st century',
  correctAnswer: '23rd century',
},
{
  question: 'About how many times was the phrase, "Beam me up, Scotty" used in the series?',
  answer1: '450',
  answer2: '238',
  answer3: '1',
  answer4: '0',
  correctAnswer: '0',
},
  // ------------------------------------------------------------
  {
    question: 'Why did Paramount try to offload "Star Trek?"',
    answer1: 'It was losing money',
    answer2: 'It was too controversial',
    answer3: 'Gene Roddenberry was impossible to work with',
    answer4: 'There were too many conflicts between the actors',
    correctAnswer: 'It was losing money',
  },
  {
    question: 'What skin color did Gene Roddenberry initially imagine for Spock?',
    answer1: 'Red',
    answer2: 'Blue',
    answer3: 'Purple',
    answer4: 'Green',
    correctAnswer: 'Red',
  },
  {
    question: 'How many total episodes were there?',
    answer1: '48',
    answer2: '67',
    answer3: '79',
    answer4: '110',
    correctAnswer: '79',
  },
  {
    question: 'Who convinced Nichelle Nicols to remain on the show in spite of on-the-job racism?',
    answer1: 'Ralph Abernathy',
    answer2: 'Rosa Parks',
    answer3: 'Martin Luther King Jr',
    answer4: 'Gene Roddenberry',
    correctAnswer: 'Martin Luther King Jr',
  },
  {
    question: 'In the show, blue shirts indicated that crew members were a part of which team?',
    answer1: 'Science',
    answer2: 'Security',
    answer3: 'Communications',
    answer4: 'Engineering',
    correctAnswer: 'Science',
  },
  {
    question: 'Who invented the Klingon language?',
    answer1: 'James Doohan',
    answer2: 'Leonard Nimoy',
    answer3: 'George Takei',
    answer4: 'Walter Koenig',
    correctAnswer: 'James Doohan',
  },  
  ];